Goodbye Christopher Robin is a family, history,
drama film directed by Simon Curtis.
The behind the scenes story of the life of A.A.
Milne and the creation of the Winnie the Pooh stories
inspired by his son Christopher Robin.
Alan Alexander Milne / Blue, played by Domhnall Gleeson.
Daphne Milne, played by Margot Robbie.
Christopher Robin Milne / Billy Moon, played by Will Tilston.
Christopher Robin Milne (Baby), played by Stanley Hamlin.
Christopher Robin Milne (Kid), played by Dexter Hyman.
Christopher Robin Milne (Kid), played by Sonny Hyman.
Goodbye Christopher Robin is a 2017 British biographical
drama film about Winnie-the-Pooh's creator A.
Milne and his family, particularly his son Christopher.
Directed by Simon Curtis and written by Frank Cottrell-Boyce and Simon Vaughan,
it stars Domhnall Gleeson, Margot Robbie, and Kelly Macdonald.
The film premiered in the United Kingdom on 29 September 2017, receiving mixed
reviews from critics and grossed $7.2 million at the box office.
The film explores themes of new york city,
jealousy, bookshop, tree house, bullying.
The tone is emotional.